perfectworld.com.my 2011-02-07

# Privacy Statement

**a) Collection and Use of Personal Information**

The information we learn from you as our valued customers helps us to personalize and continually improve our service provided in this Website.

We use the information to facilitate the communication between our company and yourself should you instruct so, communicate with you about updates of this Website, promotional offers, update our records and generally maintain your accounts with us, display content such as wish lists and customer reviews and recommend merchandise and services that might be of interest to you.

We also use this information to improve this Website and this Platform, prevent or detect fraud or abuses of this Website and enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf.

 **b) Information you give us**

We receive and store any information you enter on this Website or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. Information about our customers is an important part of our business and we are not in the business of selling it to others. We share customer information only as described below and the subsidiaries which we control and that are either subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice.

 **c) Automatic information**

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies" and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses this Website.

 **d) Information from other sources**

We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

 **e) Promotional offers**

Sometimes we send offers to selected groups of users on behalf of other businesses. When we do this, we do not give that business your name and address.

 **f) Business transfers**

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Notice (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise).

Also, in the unlikely event that our company, or substantially was sold, all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

 **g) Protection of Our Company and others**

We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law, to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements or to protect the rights, property or safety of this Website, our users or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in a way that is contrary to the commitments made in this Privacy Notice.

 **h) With your consent**

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

 **i) Conditions of Use, Notices and Revisions**

If you choose to visit this Website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Terms of Use, including limitations on damages and application of the laws of relevant jurisdiction. If you have any concern about privacy at this Website, please e-mail us a thorough description and we will try to resolve the issue for you. Our business changes constantly and the Terms of Use will change too. You are to check our website frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

 **j) Automatic Information**

Examples of the information we collect and analyse include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, login, e-mail address, password, computer and connection information such as browser type and version, your operating system and platform, purchase history, which we sometimes aggregate with similar information from other customers to create valued added features, the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from our website (including date and time), cookie number, products you viewed or searched.

 **k) Information from Other Sources**

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily, account information, purchase or redemption information and page-view information from some merchants with which we operate co-branded businesses for which we provide technical, fulfillment, advertising or other services and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers.
